[
    {
        "front": "たずねる",
        "back": "to ask, to visit",
        "chapter": "N4 C8"
    },
    {
        "front": "～め\n「～目」",
        "back": "order, sequence, or purpose,",
        "chapter": "N4 C8"
    },
    {
        "front": "かど\n「角」",
        "back": "corner",
        "chapter": "N4 C8"
    },
    {
        "front": "とおり\n「通り」",
        "back": "street",
        "chapter": "N4 C8"
    },
    {
        "front": "しばらく",
        "back": "a while",
        "chapter": "N4 C8"
    },
    {
        "front": "コンビニ",
        "back": "convenience store",
        "chapter": "N4 C8"
    },
    {
        "front": "あんない（する）\n「案内」",
        "back": "to guide",
        "chapter": "N4 C8"
    },
    {
        "front": "みち\n「道」",
        "back": "the road",
        "chapter": "N4 C8"
    },
    {
        "front": "こうさてん\n「交差点」",
        "back": "the crossing",
        "chapter": "N4 C8"
    },
    {
        "front": "しんごう\n「信号」",
        "back": "the traffic light",
        "chapter": "N4 C8"
    },
    {
        "front": "かど\n「角」",
        "back": "the corner",
        "chapter": "N4 C8"
    },
    {
        "front": "どうろ\n「道路」",
        "back": "the road",
        "chapter": "N4 C8"
    },
    {
        "front": "はし\n「橋」",
        "back": "the bridge",
        "chapter": "N4 C8"
    },
    {
        "front": "はんたい\n「反対」",
        "back": "the opposite",
        "chapter": "N4 C8"
    },
    {
        "front": "はんたい（する）\n「反対」",
        "back": "to oppose, to be opposed to",
        "chapter": "N4 C8"
    }
]